outdoorvoices.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy / Statementv

                        Privacy Policy / Statement
                        v. 2.0 — Spring, 2015
                        Section No. 1 →
                        What Do We Do With Your Information?
                        A. When you purchase from the OV store, as part of the buying and selling process,
hello@outdoorvoices.com we collect the personal information you give us—items like your Name, Address
outdoorvoices.com       and E-Mail. When you browse the OV store, we also automatically receive your
                        computer’s Internet Protocol address in order for us to glean information that
                        helps us learn about your computer’s browser and operating system.
head office
nyc —
                        B. With your permission, we may send you e-mails about our store, new prod-
No. 255 Canal St.       ucts and other updates.
Third Fl.
New York, ny
10013–3522
United States           Section No. 2 →
tel : +1 646 524 5896   Consent
flagship
atx —
                        A. How do you get my consent?
No. 606 Blanco St.          When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction,
Ground Fl.
Austin, tx
                        verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery, or return a purchase,
78703–5308              you consent to our collecting said information and using it for that specific rea-
United States
                        son (& that specific reason only). If we ask for your personal information for a
tel: +1 512 356 9136    secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your consent,
                        or provide you with an opportunity to say ‘No’ or opt-out.
                        B. How do I withdraw my consent?
                            If after you opt-in you end up having a change of heart / mind, you may with-
                        draw your consent at any time by contacting us at hello@outdoorvoices.com or
                        sending us a physical piece of mail at:
                            255 Canal St., Third Floor
                            New York, ny, 10013–3533
                            United States
                        Section No. 3 →
                        Disclosure
                        A. Respecting and protecting customer privacy is of the utmost importance to
                        us here at OV. That said, we may disclose your personal information if we are
p. 1 of 4               required by Law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

          Privacy Policy / Statement
          v. 2.0 — Spring, 2015
          Section No. 4 →
          Shopify
          A. The Outdoor Voices store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the
          online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to
          you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general
          Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
          B. Payment
               If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then
          Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card
          Industry Data Security Standard (pci-dss). Your purchase transaction data is
          stored only as long as is necessary to complete your transaction. After that is
          complete, your transaction information is deleted. All payment gateways adhere
          to the standards set by pci-dss as managed by the pci Security Standards Coun-
          cil, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, and American Express.
          pci-dss requirements help ensure the secure handling of information by Outdoor
          Voices and its service providers. For more insight, you may also read Shopify’s
          proprietary Terms of Service or Privacy Policy, available via shopify.com.
          Section No. 5 →
          Third-Party Services
          A. In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and dis-
          close your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the ser-
          vices they provide to us. However, certain third-party providers have their own
          privacy policies regarding the information we are required to provide to them for
          your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you
          read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your infor-
          mation will be handled. Note that certain providers may be located in a different
          jurisdiction than either you or OV. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction
          that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your informa-
          tion may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service
          provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada
          and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the US, then
          your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject
          to disclosure under US legislation, including the Patriot Act. Once you leave our
          store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are
p. 2 of 4 no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

          Privacy Policy / Statement
          v. 2.0 — Spring, 2015
          B. Links
              When you click on links within the Outdoor Voices shop, they may direct you
          away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites
          and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
          C. Google Analytics
              Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our website.
          Section No. 6 →
          Security
          A. To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and
          follow best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, ac-
          cessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card
          information, that information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology
          (ssl) and stored with an aes-256 encryption. Although no method of transmis-
          sion over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all pci-dss
          requirements and implement additional generally-accepted industry standards.
          Section No. 7 →
          Cookies
          A. Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you
          can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.
              session_id — Unique token; Sessional. Allows Shopify to store information
          about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).
              shopify_visit — No data held; Persistent for 30 mins. from the last visit. Used
          by our website provider’s internal tracker to record the number of visits.
              shopify_uniq — No data held; Expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of
          the next day. Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.
              cart — Unique token; Persistent for 2 wks. Stores information about the
          contents of your cart.
              secure_session_id — Unique token; Sessional.
              storefront_digest — Unique token; Indefinite. If the shop has a password,
          this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.
              google analytics pref — Persistent for a very short period; Set by Google.
p. 3 of 4 Tracks who visits the store and from where.

                        Privacy Policy / Statement
                        v. 2.0 — Spring, 2015
                        Section No. 8 →
                        Age of Consent
                        A. By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in
hello@outdoorvoices.com your state or province of residence, and that you have given us your consent to
outdoorvoices.com       allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
head office
nyc —                   Section No. 9 →
No. 255 Canal St.       Changes to This Privacy Policy
Third Fl.
New York, ny
10013–3522              A. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time; please review frequent-
United States
                        ly. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on
tel : +1 646 524 5896   the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here
flagship                that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect,
atx —                   how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and / or disclose it. If
No. 606 Blanco St.      our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be
Ground Fl.              transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
Austin, tx
78703–5308
United States
tel: +1 512 356 9136    Questions &
                        Contact Information →
                        If you would like to Access, Amend, Alter, or Delete any personal information we
                        have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact
                        us at hello@outdoorvoices.com, or send us a piece of mail at:
                            255 Canal St., Third Floor
                            New York, ny, 10013–3533
                            United States
p. 4 of 4
